The only thing harder than getting in, is staying in.
The Clique is a comedy, drama, family film directed by Michael Lembeck.
A young girl tries to fit in with a clique of popular middle school girls
after moving into the guest house of one of their homes.
Massie Block, played by Elizabeth McLaughlin.
Claire Lyons, played by Ellen Marlow.
Kristen Gregory, played by Bridgit Mendler.
Alicia Rivera, played by Samantha Boscarino.
Dylan Marvil, played by Sophie Anna Everhard.
Judy Lyons, played by Elizabeth Keifer.
The Clique is a 2008 American teen comedy-drama film directed by Michael Lembeck from a screenplay by
Liz Tigelaar, based on the young adult novel series of the same name by Lisi Harrison.
The film was produced by Alloy Entertainment and Tyra Banks' company
Bankable Productions, and was released on November 11, 2008.
It stars Elizabeth McLaughlin and Ellen Marlow, with Bridgit Mendler,
Samantha Boscarino, and Sophie Anna Everhard in supporting roles.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.